smallcapnetwork.com 2010-06-18

# Privacy Policy : Documents : Small Cap Stocks and Penny Stocks For Big Returns - SmallCap Network

Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience with the SmallCap Network as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to visit our website with complete confidence.

SmallCap Network (herein referred to as "SCN") has created a privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

By visiting SCN's web site(s), Members agree to the Terms & Conditions outlined within our Terms of Use Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Email Policy. It is the Member's responsibility to read and understand these three SCN documents (Terms of Use Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Email Policy) prior to reviewing any information from SCN, signing up for any free newsletter service, or submitting any personal information through our site. SCN may update or revise its Terms of Use Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Email Policy, and we encourage you to periodically review these documents for our most recent policies.

TGR Group, LLC publishes and manages SmallCapNetwork.com.

## Information SCN Gathers and Tracks

SCN gathers many pieces of information for use in fulfilling Member requests. This information includes, but is not limited to name, email address, phone number, postal address, billing address, IP address, time and date login information. This information is used to fulfill requests and allows our staff to better serve Members.

SCN also gathers information about how Members access and use SCN's services through smallcapnetwork.com, including how often and when Members visit the website, IP addresses, and the URL of the Member's last visit. This information is used solely for SCN's internal business purposes and will not be shared with any third parties.

The information that SCN collects is kept confidential unless otherwise specified. SCN uses third party advertisers who are interested in targeting our Members on behalf of their advertisers.

## Registration Pages & Advertising

SCN collects Member information at the time of registration through Smallcapnetwork.com. This information is collected by SCN and stored on our secure web server. This information is only shared with SCN's partner, Marketbyte, LLC, owner and operator of OTCJournal.com. Otherwise, this information is held strictly confidential by SCN.

SCN often offers selected offers from our partners as part of the registration process for certain sites, services, and products. These offers are designed to assist Members by providing them with valuable information, products, and services from partners who we believe will complement a Members interests. SCN in no way endorses the products or services of these advertisers. When a Member selects to receive one of our partner's offers, they are agreeing to receive information from that advertiser. As part of this advertising program, SCN will provide the advertiser with the required information required to fulfill the Members request. This includes, but is not limited to name, postal address, email address, and phone number.

## Marketing Messages from Third Party Sponsors

SCN offers free subscription email newsletters via SmallCap Network and OTC Journal.

Subscription requires Members to provide us with an email address and name at time of registration. Members may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter. We operate in compliance with CAN-SPAM legislation, and maintain a "Do Not Mail" list of email addresses which will not receive future correspondence from SCN. Instructions for adding an email address to this "Do Not Mail" list are specified within email correspondence from SCN (with the exception of paid subscription newsletter issues).

Email addresses provided to SCN are kept on a secure server. SCN does however make available both email and postal information to selected advertisers. Email advertisers who wish to advertise to SCN's members are required to comply with CAN-SPAM legislation, and provide Members with an easy process of removing from future offers, as well as provide a "Do Not Mail" option for members who do not wish to receive any further communication from a specific advertiser. Members can elect to receive offers directly from SCN as well as sponsorship messages from our partners. Members can elect to discontinue receiving third party advertisements from SCN, while continuing to receive free newsletter content. SCN will not sell to third parties the personally identifiable information of our subscribers except in connection with the sale of all or substantially all of SCN's assets.

SCN does maintain a postal mailing list that is made available to approved advertisers who are offering financial-related products. SCN may share such postal information with such advertisers.

SCN does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly.

## Delete/Deactivate Policy

Members may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter, or through our web site. This includes being permanently removed from our list of active subscribers to ensure that you do not receive further communications from SCN.

## Email Policy

We understand the serious concerns regarding email advertising. As a result, we created a separate Email Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our Members and desire to send email communication only to those Members who wish to receive communications from SCN.

Should you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy or other related issues, please contact us so that we can address your concerns.

TGR Group, LLC  
4653 Carmel Mtn. Rd Suite 308 #402  
San Diego, CA 92130  
Email: [info@smallcapnetwork.com](mailto:info@smallcapnetwork.com)

## EMAIL POLICY AGREEMENT

As of March 30 2009, SCN Group, LLC ("SCN") has created an Email Policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and dedication to sending email communications only to those who have specifically requested such information. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our company and our web sites.

By visiting SCN's web site(s), Members agree to the Terms & Conditions outlined within our Terms of Use Agreement, Privacy Policy and Email Policy. It is the Member's responsibility to read and understand these three SCN documents (Terms of Use Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Email Policy) prior to reviewing any information from SCN, signing up for any free or paid subscription newsletter service, or submitting any personal information to our firm. SCN may update or revise its Terms of Use Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Email Policy from time to time, and we encourage you to periodically review these documents for our most recent policies.

SCN is a publisher of free investment newsletters to individuals.

We allow Members to visit our web site, complete a form, and in doing so agree to receive our free email newsletter(s), including our Sister site's free email newsletter, the OTC Journal located at www.otcjournal.com.

We offer our free newsletters to Members through partner web sites and web sites where we advertise, and directly through our own web site.

Members who do not wish to receive future issues of free newsletters by email should follow the instructions within this Email Policy or within a specific email communication from SCN.

## Email Advertisements

We utilize email as a communication channel to send information regarding our products and services to our current subscribers. We send these email messages only to individuals who have directly requested information from our firm (i.e. signed up for our free newsletters) or have or in the past have had a direct relationship with our firm (i.e. a previous customer).

WE ALLOW ANY CURRENT OR FORMER CUSTOMER OR RECIPIENT OF A FREE EMAIL NEWSLETTER FROM SCN TO CHOOSE TO DISCONTINUE RECEIVING EMAIL MESSAGES FROM OUR COMPANY AT ANY TIME. See "Discontinuance of Emails" below.

## Third Party Email Advertising

We occasionally advertise via email with qualified third party companies that are managing their email database(s) of subscribers in accordance with CAN-SPAM legislation and best industry practices. When we advertise by email through a third party or through an agency, we do so in accordance with the following:

The advertisement is sent only to users who have agreed to receive ADVERTISEMENT or SPECIAL OFFER emails from the list owner.

The advertisement is sent FROM the company owning the email list.

The advertisement is clearly marked as an ADVERTISEMENT or SPECIAL OFFER.

The firm managing the email list has clear instructions and functionality in place for prompt removal from the email list.

Our contact information is made available so that recipients can contact us and instruct us not to send future advertisements.

We occasionally send email advertisements and offers to our members on behalf of third party advertisers or agencies acting on their behalf, in accordance with CAN-SPAM legislation and best industry practices. PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OF MEMBERS WILL NOT BE SOLD TO A THIRD PARTY ADVERTISER EXCEPT IN CONNECTION WITH THE SALE OF ALL OR SUBSTANTIALLY ALL OF SCN'S ASSETS.

However, as part of this advertising program, SCN will provide the advertiser with the required information required to fulfill the Members request. This includes, but is not limited to name, postal address, email address, and phone number. When we send an advertisement or special offer on behalf of a third party or through an agency, we do so in accordance with the following:

The advertisement is sent FROM SCN or the specific newsletter to which the recipient is automatically subscribed (i.e. OTC Journal).

The advertisement is clearly marked as an ADVERTISEMENT or SPECIAL OFFER.

There are clear instructions and functionality in place for prompt removal from the email list.

Our contact information is made available so that recipients can contact us and instruct us not to send future advertisements.

## Discontinuance of Emails

In accordance with CAN-SPAM legislation, it is our policy to include instructions and means for removal from our database at any time in an automated fashion. We provide instructions for removal at the bottom of every email sent from our company.

At the bottom of each email communication we include detailed instructions for removal from our email lists, including:

  * Displaying the recipient's email address that is in our database and receiving the message.
  * Providing a customized URL that allows the recipient to click to our web site and automatically manage their subscriptions, including canceling all email subscriptions or selecting to receive no further messages from our firm.
  * An active email address to contact us in order to request manual removal or discontinuance of future email messages from our firm.
  * Our postal address for mailing a formal request to our firm.

At our web site, we allow subscribers to manage their subscriptions, including:

  * Choose to discontinue a subscription.
  * Change their email address.
  * Opt-in to start receiving our newsletter (s).

SCN maintains a DO NOT MAIL LIST. This is a list of subscribers who have decided that they never wish to receive another message from our firm. These email addresses are collected and maintained in a separate file in our database. These individuals will not receive future emails from SCN, including free email newsletters, advertisements directly from SCN, or advertisements from third party advertisers sent on our behalf. Email addresses on this list will not receive future email messages from our firm. Subscribers are encouraged to make sure that the address receiving emails from SCN is in fact the same address in our database by clicking the unique URL at the end of an email message from our firm, or forwarding the received email communication to our customer service department so that we may see which email address was the recipient of an email from our firm.

Should you have any questions regarding our Email Policy or other privacy related issues, please contact us so that we can address your concerns.

TGR Group, LLC  
4653 Carmel Mtn. Rd Suite 308 #402  
San Diego, CA 92130  
Email: [info@smallcapnetwork.com](mailto:info@smallcapnetwork.com)

**USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY.**
